Donald Schein Papers
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- 1986, Capital Region, Program, nam_apap209-731 (Box 28, Folder 17-20)
- 1986, Chain of Command, nam_apap209-732 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- 1986, Channels, nam_apap209-733 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- 1986, Computer System, nam_apap209-734 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- 1986, Corporation for Public Broadcasting (CPB) Directory, nam_apap209-735 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- 1986, CPB Seminar on Management Strategy, nam_apap209-736 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- 1986, Current (Periodical), nam_apap209-737 (Box 29, Folder 1-3)
- 1986, Current Publishing Committee, nam_apap209-738 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- 1986, Daily Calendar, 1986 January-1986 July; nam_apap209-739 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- 1986, Daily Calendar, 1986 August-1986 September; nam_apap209-740 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- 1986, Daily Calendar, 1986 October-1987 January; nam_apap209-741 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- 1986, Day-Timer, 1986 January; nam_apap209-742 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- 1986, Day-Timer, 1986 February; nam_apap209-743 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- 1986, Day-Timer, 1986 March; nam_apap209-744 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- 1986, Day-Timer, 1986 April; nam_apap209-745 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- 1986, Day-Timer, 1986 May; nam_apap209-746 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- 1986, Day-Timer, 1986 June; nam_apap209-747 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- 1986, Day-Timer, 1986 July; nam_apap209-748 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- 1986, Day-Timer, 1986 August; nam_apap209-749 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- 1986, Day-Timer, 1986 September; nam_apap209-750 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- 1986, Day-Timer, 1986 October; nam_apap209-751 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- 1986, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1986 November; nam_apap209-752 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- 1986, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1986 December; nam_apap209-753 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- 1986, Development Committee, nam_apap209-754 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- 1986, Division Heads, nam_apap209-755 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- 1986, Eastern Educational Television Network, nam_apap209-756 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- 1986, Eastern Educational Television Network (EEN) Board Meeting, 1986 September 14-1986 September 16; nam_apap209-757 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- 1986, Eastern Educational Television Network Board of Trustees Meeting, 1986 September 15; nam_apap209-758 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- 1986, EITV (periodical), nam_apap209-759 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- 1986, Endowment Committee, nam_apap209-760 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- 1986, Faces of the City, Program, 1986-1987; nam_apap209-761 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- 1986, Governance & Management Handbook for Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-762 (Box 29, Folder 28)
- 1986, General Manager Search Committee, nam_apap209-763 (Box 29, Folder 29)
- 1986, Grimmer, Jean, Pending Memoranda, nam_apap209-764 (Box 29, Folder 30-31)
- 1986, Instructional Television (ITV), nam_apap209-765 (Box 29, Folder 32-34)
- 1986, Journal, nam_apap209-766 (Box 29, Folder 35)
- 1986, Life Insurance, nam_apap209-767 (Box 29, Folder 36)
- 1986, Mid-Hudson FM Transmitter, nam_apap209-768 (Box 29, Folder 37)
- 1986, "Must Carry" Legislation, nam_apap209-769 (Box 29, Folder 38)
- 1986, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-770 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- 1986, New York Network, nam_apap209-771 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- 1986, Nominating Committee, nam_apap209-772 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- 1986, NTIA Grant Application, nam_apap209-773 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- 1986, PBS Home Video Service, nam_apap209-774 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- 1986, PBS Marketing Seminar, nam_apap209-775 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- 1986, PBS Programming Pipeline, nam_apap209-776 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- 1986, PBS Selects (Home Video Service), nam_apap209-777 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- 1986, Poughkeepsie Transmitter, 1986-1987; nam_apap209-778 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- 1986, Project Development Proposals, nam_apap209-779 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- 1986, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-780 (Box 30, Folder 11-25)
- 1986, Public Relations Director Search Committee, nam_apap209-781 (Box 30, Folder 26)
- 1986, Public Relations Director Search Committee, nam_apap209-782 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- 1986, RISE-ing Stars (Telethon), nam_apap209-783 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- 1986, Search Committee, nam_apap209-784 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- 1986, Spector, Beryl -- Memorial, nam_apap209-785 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- 1986, Standard Operating Procedure Manual [Draft?], nam_apap209-786 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- 1986, Strategic Planning for PBS: A Report To PBS Member Stations, nam_apap209-787 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- 1986, Tangarone, Tony -- Pending Memoranda, nam_apap209-788 (Box 31, Folder 7-8)
- 1986, Union Negotiations, nam_apap209-789 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- 1986, VHF Drop -- In, nam_apap209-790 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- 1986, Williams, Robert -- Computer Installation, nam_apap209-791 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- 1986, Wine Tasting, nam_apap209-792 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- 1986, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-793 (Box 31, Folder 13-26)
- 1986, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-794 (Box 32, Folder 1-4)
- 1986, WMHT-FM Internal Records, nam_apap209-795 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- 1986, WMHT -- Report on Health Insurance Plan, nam_apap209-796 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- 1986, WMHT Trustee's Manual, nam_apap209-797 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- 1986, WWCN Prospective Purchase, 1986-1987; nam_apap209-798 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- 1987, Board of Trustees, nam_apap209-799 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- 1987, By-Laws Committee, nam_apap209-800 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- 1987, Capital Fund Drive, nam_apap209-801 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- 1987, Capital Region (Program), nam_apap209-802 (Box 32, Folder 12-14)
- 1987, Capital Region Magazine -- Notes and Memoranda, nam_apap209-803 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- 1987, Conferences, nam_apap209-804 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- 1987, Correspondence, nam_apap209-805 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- 1987, Current (Periodical), nam_apap209-806 (Box 32, Folder 18-22)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 January; nam_apap209-807 (Box 32, Folder 23)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 February; nam_apap209-808 (Box 32, Folder 24)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 March; nam_apap209-809 (Box 32, Folder 25)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 April; nam_apap209-810 (Box 32, Folder 26)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 May; nam_apap209-811 (Box 32, Folder 27)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 June; nam_apap209-812 (Box 32, Folder 28)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 July; nam_apap209-813 (Box 32, Folder 29)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 August; nam_apap209-814 (Box 32, Folder 30)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 September; nam_apap209-815 (Box 32, Folder 31)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 October; nam_apap209-816 (Box 32, Folder 32)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 November; nam_apap209-817 (Box 32, Folder 33)
- 1987, Day-Timer, 1987 December; nam_apap209-818 (Box 32, Folder 34)
- 1987, Fact Finders WMHT Opinion Survey, nam_apap209-819 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- 1987, Journal, nam_apap209-820 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- 1987, WUSV Purchase Proposal, nam_apap209-821 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- 1987, Kingston FM Translator, nam_apap209-822 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- 1987, Local Programming, nam_apap209-823 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- 1987, National Association of Public Television Stations (NAPTS) St. Louis Convention, nam_apap209-824 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- 1987, New Paltz FM Transmitter, nam_apap209-825 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- 1987, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-826 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- 1987, Petersburgh Property, nam_apap209-827 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- 1987, Proctor's Theatre Development Fund Brochures, nam_apap209-828 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- 1987, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-829 (Box 33, Folder 11-19)
- 1987, Quiet Campaign Testimonial Letters, nam_apap209-830 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- 1987, Report of the PBS Special Committee on Program Policies and Procedures, nam_apap209-831 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- 1987, Retirement, nam_apap209-832 (Box 33, Folder 22-24)
- 1987, Ricotta, Kitty, nam_apap209-833 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- 1987, Soviet Satellite Project, nam_apap209-834 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- 1987, WMHT Financial Statements, nam_apap209-835 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- 1987, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-836 (Box 33, Folder 28-34)
- 1987, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-837 (Box 34, Folder 1-4)
- 1987, WMHT Internal Records and News Clippings, nam_apap209-838 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- 1987, WMHT Internal Records and News Clippings, 1987 May-1987 June; nam_apap209-839 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- 1987, WMHT Internal Records and News Clippings, 1987 June; nam_apap209-840 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- 1987, WMHT Internal Records and News Clippings, 1987 July; nam_apap209-841 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- 1987, WMHT Internal Records and News Clippings, 1987 July-1987 August; nam_apap209-842 (Box 34, Folder 9-10)
- 1987, WMHT Trustee's Manual, nam_apap209-843 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- 1987, WMHT 25th Anniversary Celebration, nam_apap209-844 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- 1987, WMHT 25th Anniversary Program, nam_apap209-845 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- 1987, WMHT Video Recollections, nam_apap209-846 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- 1987, WMHT Video Recollections -- Interviews Transcripts, nam_apap209-847 (Box 34, Folder 15-17)
- 1988, Capital Region (Program), nam_apap209-848 (Box 34, Folder 18-21)
- 1988, Current (Periodical), nam_apap209-849 (Box 34, Folder 22-24)
- 1988, Daily Calendar, 1988 January-1988 February; nam_apap209-850 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- 1988, Day-Timer, 1988 March; nam_apap209-851 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- 1988, Day-Timer, 1988 April; nam_apap209-852 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- 1988, Day-Timer, 1988 June; nam_apap209-853 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- 1988, Day-Timer, 1988 July; nam_apap209-854 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- 1988, Day-Timer, 1988 August; nam_apap209-855 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- 1988, Day-Timer, 1988 September; nam_apap209-856 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- 1988, Day-Timer, 1988 October; nam_apap209-857 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- 1988, Day-Timer, 1988 November; nam_apap209-858 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- 1988, Day-Timer, 1988 December; nam_apap209-859 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- 1988, Donald Schein Testimonial Dinner, 04/14/1988; nam_apap209-860 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- 1988, Donald Schein Tribute Dinner, 04/14/1988; nam_apap209-861 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- 1988, Donald Schein Tribute Dinner -- Guestbook, 04/14/1988; nam_apap209-862 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- 1988, Johanson, Patricia, nam_apap209-863 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- 1988, Journal, nam_apap209-864 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- 1988, Missouri Travel Guide (Publication), nam_apap209-865 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- 1988, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-866 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- 1988, Proctor's, nam_apap209-867 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- 1988, Proctor's, 1988-1995; nam_apap209-868 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- 1988, Proctor's Steering Committee, nam_apap209-869 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- 1988, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-870 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- 1988, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-871 (Box 35, Folder 22)
- 1988, The Public Broadcasting Report (periodical), nam_apap209-872 (Box 35, Folder 23)
- 1988, Russia Trip, nam_apap209-873 (Box 35, Folder 24)
- 1988, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-874 (Box 35, Folder 25-27)
- 1989, Alumni Giving, nam_apap209-875 (Box 35, Folder 28)
- 1989, Capital (Program), nam_apap209-876 (Box 35, Folder 29-31)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 January; nam_apap209-877 (Box 35, Folder 32)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 February; nam_apap209-878 (Box 35, Folder 33)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 March; nam_apap209-879 (Box 35, Folder 34)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 April; nam_apap209-880 (Box 35, Folder 35)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 May; nam_apap209-881 (Box 35, Folder 36)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 June; nam_apap209-882 (Box 35, Folder 37)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 July; nam_apap209-883 (Box 35, Folder 38)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 August; nam_apap209-884 (Box 35, Folder 39)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 September; nam_apap209-885 (Box 35, Folder 40)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 October; nam_apap209-886 (Box 35, Folder 41)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 November; nam_apap209-887 (Box 35, Folder 42)
- 1989, Day-Timer, 1989 December; nam_apap209-888 (Box 35, Folder 43)
- 1989, Environmental Clearinghouse of Schenectady (ECOS), nam_apap209-889 (Box 35, Folder 44)
- 1989, Fundraising, 1989-1991; nam_apap209-890 (Box 35, Folder 45)
- 1989, Journal, nam_apap209-891 (Box 35, Folder 46)
- 1989, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-892 (Box 35, Folder 47)
- 1989, Proctor's, nam_apap209-893 (Box 35, Folder 48-50)
- 1989, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-894 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- 1989, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-895 (Box 36, Folder 2-3)
- 1990, Capital (Program), nam_apap209-896 (Box 36, Folder 4-6)
- 1990, Current (Periodical), nam_apap209-897 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 January; nam_apap209-898 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 February; nam_apap209-899 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 March; nam_apap209-900 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 April; nam_apap209-901 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 May; nam_apap209-902 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 June; nam_apap209-903 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 July; nam_apap209-904 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 August; nam_apap209-905 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 September; nam_apap209-906 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 October; nam_apap209-907 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 November; nam_apap209-908 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- 1990, Day-Timer, 1990 December; nam_apap209-909 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- 1990, Journal, nam_apap209-910 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- 1990, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-911 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- 1990, Proctor's, nam_apap209-912 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- 1990, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-913 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- 1990, Travel Master Recreational Vehicle, nam_apap209-914 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- 1990, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-915 (Box 36, Folder 25)
- 1991, Comint (Periodical), nam_apap209-916 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- 1991, Current (Periodical), nam_apap209-917 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- 1991, Friedman, Howard, nam_apap209-918 (Box 36, Folder 28)
- 1991, News Clippings, General (Newsprint), nam_apap209-919 (Box 36, Folder 29)
- 1991, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-920 (Box 36, Folder 30)
- 1991, News Clippings on WMHT, Newsprint, nam_apap209-921 (Box 36, Folder 31)
- 1991, Proctor's Theater Guild, nam_apap209-922 (Box 36, Folder 32)
- 1991, Program Guide/Prelude (Program), nam_apap209-923 (Box 36, Folder 33)
- 1991, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-924 (Box 36, Folder 34)
- 1991, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-925 (Box 36, Folder 35-36)
- 1991, WMHT Production Services Packet, nam_apap209-926 (Box 36, Folder 37)
- 1992, Comint (Periodical), nam_apap209-927 (Box 36, Folder 38)
- 1992, Correspondence, nam_apap209-928 (Box 36, Folder 39)
- 1992, Correspondence with Legislators and Related Material, 1992-1993; nam_apap209-929 (Box 36, Folder 40)
- 1992, Current (Periodical), nam_apap209-930 (Box 36, Folder 41-43)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 January; nam_apap209-931 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 February; nam_apap209-932 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 March; nam_apap209-933 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 April; nam_apap209-934 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 May; nam_apap209-935 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 June; nam_apap209-936 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 July; nam_apap209-937 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 August; nam_apap209-938 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 September; nam_apap209-939 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 October; nam_apap209-940 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 November; nam_apap209-941 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- 1992, Day-Timer, 1992 December; nam_apap209-942 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- 1992, Journal, nam_apap209-943 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- 1992, News Clippings on Broadcasting, nam_apap209-944 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- 1992, News Clippings, General (Newsprint), nam_apap209-945 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- 1992, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-946 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- 1992, Prelude (Program), nam_apap209-947 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- 1992, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-948 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- 1992, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-949 (Box 37, Folder 19-20)
- 1992, WMHT Station Histories, 1953-1992; nam_apap209-950 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- 1993, Comint (Periodical), Autumn 1993; nam_apap209-951 (Box 37, Folder 22)
- 1993, Current (Periodical), nam_apap209-952 (Box 37, Folder 23-26)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 January; nam_apap209-953 (Box 37, Folder 27)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 February; nam_apap209-954 (Box 37, Folder 28)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 March; nam_apap209-955 (Box 37, Folder 29)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 April; nam_apap209-956 (Box 37, Folder 30)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 May; nam_apap209-957 (Box 37, Folder 31)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 June; nam_apap209-958 (Box 37, Folder 32)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 July; nam_apap209-959 (Box 37, Folder 33)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 August; nam_apap209-960 (Box 37, Folder 34)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 September; nam_apap209-961 (Box 37, Folder 35)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 October; nam_apap209-962 (Box 37, Folder 36)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 November; nam_apap209-963 (Box 37, Folder 37)
- 1993, Day-Timer, 1993 December; nam_apap209-964 (Box 37, Folder 38)
- 1993, Journal, nam_apap209-965 (Box 37, Folder 39)
- 1993, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-966 (Box 37, Folder 40)
- 1993, Prelude, Program, nam_apap209-967 (Box 37, Folder 41)
- 1993, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-968 (Box 37, Folder 42)
- 1993, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-969 (Box 37, Folder 43)
- 1994, Current (Periodical), nam_apap209-970 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- 1994, Day-Timer, 1994 January; nam_apap209-971 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- 1994, Day-Timer, 1994 February; nam_apap209-972 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- 1994, Day-Timer, 1994 March; nam_apap209-973 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- 1994, Day-Timer, 1994 April; nam_apap209-974 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- 1994, Day-Timer, 1994 May; nam_apap209-975 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- 1994, Day-Timer, 1994 June; nam_apap209-976 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- 1994, Day-Timer, 1994 July; nam_apap209-977 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- 1994, Journal, nam_apap209-978 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- 1994, Journal, nam_apap209-979 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- 1994, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-980 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- 1994, Prelude (Program), nam_apap209-981 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- 1994, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-982 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- 1994, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-983 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- 1994, WMHT Long Range Plan, nam_apap209-984 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- 1995, Correspondence, nam_apap209-985 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 January; nam_apap209-986 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 February; nam_apap209-987 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 March; nam_apap209-988 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 April; nam_apap209-989 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 May; nam_apap209-990 (Box 38, Folder 21)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 June; nam_apap209-991 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 July; nam_apap209-992 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 August; nam_apap209-993 (Box 38, Folder 24)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 September; nam_apap209-994 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 October; nam_apap209-995 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 November; nam_apap209-996 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 December; nam_apap209-997 (Box 38, Folder 28)
- 1995, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-998 (Box 38, Folder 29)
- 1995, Prelude, Program, nam_apap209-999 (Box 38, Folder 30)
- 1995, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-1000 (Box 38, Folder 31)
- 1996, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-1001 (Box 38, Folder 32)
- 1996, Prelude (Program), nam_apap209-1002 (Box 38, Folder 33)
- 1996, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-1003 (Box 38, Folder 34)
- 1997, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-1004 (Box 38, Folder 35)
- 1997, Notes, nam_apap209-1005 (Box 38, Folder 36)
- 1997, Prelude (Program), nam_apap209-1006 (Box 38, Folder 37)
- 1998, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-1007 (Box 38, Folder 38)
- 1998, Prelude, Program, nam_apap209-1008 (Box 38, Folder 39)
- 1998, Station History, nam_apap209-1009 (Box 38, Folder 40)
- 1999, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-1010 (Box 38, Folder 41)
- 1999, Prelude, Program, nam_apap209-1011 (Box 38, Folder 42)
- 2000, Prelude, Program, nam_apap209-1012 (Box 38, Folder 43)
- 2001, Prelude, Program, nam_apap209-1013 (Box 38, Folder 44)
- 2002, Prelude/Outlook, Program, nam_apap209-1014 (Box 38, Folder 45)
- 2003, Outlook, Program, nam_apap209-1015 (Box 38, Folder 46)
- 2004, Outlook, Program, nam_apap209-1016 (Box 38, Folder 47)
- 2005, Outlook, Program, nam_apap209-1017 (Box 38, Folder 48)
- Educational Television/Public Broadcasting, Undated; nam_apap209-1018 (Box 38, Folder 49)
- News Clippings on WMHT, Undated; nam_apap209-1019 (Box 38, Folder 50)
- WMHT Internal Records, Undated; nam_apap209-1020 (Box 38, Folder 51)
- MHCET Promotional Photographs, 1954-1956; nam_apap209-1021 (Box 39, Folder 1-6)
- Articles on MHCET Foreign Language Broadcasts, 1956; nam_apap209-1022 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Producing Your Educational Television Program, MHCET Publication, 1961; nam_apap209-1023 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- WMHT Promotional Photographs, Contact Sheets and Negatives, 1961-1962; nam_apap209-1024 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- VHF Station Announcement Negatives, 1962?; nam_apap209-1025 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Family Photographs, Contact Sheets and Negatives, 1963; nam_apap209-1026 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Aerial Photographs of Transmitter Site, 1970-1972; nam_apap209-1027 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Contact Sheet and Negatives, Baltimore EEN Meeting, 1977; nam_apap209-1028 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Family Photographs, 1980s?; nam_apap209-1029 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Negatives, nam_apap209-1030 (Box 40, Folder 6-7)
- Promotional Photos, Loose, nam_apap209-1031 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Promotional Photos, nam_apap209-1032 (Box 40, Folder 9-12)
- Promotional Photos, Loose, nam_apap209-1033 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Promotional Photos, nam_apap209-1034 (Box 41, Folder 2-6)
- Promotional Photos, Loose, Mostly WMHT-FM?, nam_apap209-1035 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Promotional Photos, nam_apap209-1036 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Portrait Photographs, Various Individuals, nam_apap209-1037 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Promotional Photos, Station History, nam_apap209-1038 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Trustee Portraits, nam_apap209-1039 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Photographs, Executive Mansion, Albany, Fundraising Event?, 1960s?; nam_apap209-1040 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Contact Sheets and Negatives, nam_apap209-1041 (Box 41, Folder 13-14)
- Contact Sheets and Negatives, Loose, nam_apap209-1042 (Box 41, Folder 15)